

SITI NOR NAJIA IBRAHIM

A competent Bachelor of Science graduate, very passionate to learn and grow with 1 year and 5 month working experience with Project Management System for Petroliam Nasional Berhad (PETRONAS). I am currently looking for a full-time working position. I would like to work with other professionals in an organized environment, where I can utilize my skills and gain experiences throughout my contribution in the company.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

June 2016 – Oct 2017

> Kuala Lumpur

CJP Engineering (M) Sdn. Bhd.

System Administrator/Executive

- Responsible to attend inquiry from client (PETRONAS)
- ✓ Responsible to control the registration of the system user
- ✓ Gather feedback from client from time to time
- ✓ Prepare communication pack on weekly basis

May 2012 – Sept 2012

Klang

KIMEADA Sdn. Bhd.

Production Team

- Experience in managing process of import and export of goods in the warehouse
- ✓ Support the respond for daily delivery order from client
- ✓ Monitor the quantity and quality of goods in the warehouse
- ✓ Report to client on the condition of goods in the warehouse

CONTACT



Lot 3519, Batu 11 1/4, Jalan Kapar, 42200 Kapar, Selangor



jianadira@gmail.com



+6018-668 4821

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Microsoft Words

90%

Microsoft PowerPoint

80%

Microsoft Exels

70%

LANGUAGES

English (MUET: Band 3)

FINAL YEAR PROJECT

Nanowire's on Electrical Properties

on Indium Antimonide (InSb) Using

The Effect of Diameter of

70%

95%

Bahasa Malaysia

EDUCATION

2012 - 2016 Universiti Putra Malaysia

Bachelor Sciences (Hons) Major in Material Science

CGPA: 3.02

2012 Perak Matriculation College

Science CGPA: 3.20

2009 - 2010

Sepang Technical School

Science (Civil Engineering)

PERSONAL SKILL

- Good interpersonal skill, determined, optimistic and time managing
- Fast learner, flexible and able to accommodate in most working environment
- Flexible, willing to relocate, willing to work overtime and able to work effectively in a team

REFERENCES

Contact Pad

1. Dr. Nor Kamilah Saat

Senior Lecturer & Academic Advicer,

+603 – 894 6681 kamilah@upm.edu.my

2. Nurulhuda Che Azami

Executive@ PETRONAS Project Management +6017- 452 5472

nurulhuda_azami@petronas.com

$\mathfrak{P}_{\mathsf{R}}$

REWARD AND ACHIVEMENT

- 1. The Highest Student Council (Leadership & Volunteering), Kolej Tun Perak, UPM in 2015
- 2. Comitte Members of (krew) for MAPURA 2014 (Final Year Dinner Event)
- 3. Secreatary of Physics Fusion Day 2014
- 4. The Highest Student Council (Secretariat of Human Resources), Kolej Tun Perak, UPM in 2014